Ashiana.Griffith: Hi, Julia.
Julia Matveyev: Hello.
Ashiana.Griffith: Hey, sorry for the late. I just couldn't figure out how to like log in to that link.
Julia Matveyev: Oh, no worries.
Ashiana.Griffith: It kept saying… it kept giving me, like, error, like, not now, like, the meeting's not now, or, like, not today. And then I just… then I saw it popped up, and then it said it starts in 51 minutes.
Julia Matveyev: Yeah, that's kind of what happened for me. I just was idling on it and then it just kind of appeared.
Julia Matveyev: Bye.
Ashiana.Griffith: Hi.
Ashiana.Griffith: I thought I was… I thought I was gonna be late, because, on my phone, they have a, like,
Ashiana.Griffith: My time in Texas, and then my computer, because I…
Ashiana.Griffith: My computer's in Easter time, so on my phone I saw, like,
Ashiana.Griffith: 4:40. Sorry, at first I'm like, am I early for this meeting? Then I looked at the computer, I'm like, oh my god, oh my god.
Julia Matveyev: Yeah.
Julia Matveyev: Well… It's… it's fine. Muhammad isn't even here.
Julia Matveyev: I do have a question. I, unfortunately.
Julia Matveyev: Do you have to leave by 3? Like, this is a rarity. That's fine.
Ashiana.Griffith: Do you want to go, like, now? Like, I mean, we've… I don't… I don't mind, because I don't have much to talk about. I know that we're supposed to meet later in the week for the rest of what we discussed, and I started on that, so I'm not going to go into detail.
Ashiana.Griffith: I think the meeting today was mostly for, like, the LLC in terms of the name before we can quite proceed. So, I mean, if you wanna, like,
Ashiana.Griffith: Leave now, we can both, like.
Ashiana.Griffith: Leave now, and then… I'll text in the legal team.
Ashiana.Griffith: If it's, like, are we gonna reschedule or not? And if not, I'll just, I'll pop back on.
Ashiana.Griffith: If you want to do that.
Julia Matveyev: I mean, we could just…
Julia Matveyev: I don't think, kind of, sharing too much information is going to be particularly useful, since we haven't really had that much time to work on things, but, like.
Julia Matveyev: I mean, I've started some work on the, what, like, terms and conditions, haven't really… don't have much to say about that. You mean the same exact spot I was with the LLC?
Ashiana.Griffith: I mean, like, for me, there's nothing to share, because I know that we were gonna go over that, like.
Ashiana.Griffith: During the week next week, and today was basically just for the LLC name.
Ashiana.Griffith: to quite proceed, so I… besides that, I don't have much to say either.
Julia Matveyev: All right.
Ashiana.Griffith: Alright.
Ashiana.Griffith: Alright, Ben, I think we're good to go.
Julia Matveyev: Probably, yeah.
Ashiana.Griffith: If ever, if ever Mohammed says anything, then I'll, I'll just, I'll just join on or something.
Julia Matveyev: I mean, I'll be online until roughly 3.
Ashiana.Griffith: Yeah.
Julia Matveyev: Because that's when I largely have to, like, start getting ready to get out of the house. Yeah. So, like.
Julia Matveyev: If I'm necessary, like, if I'm needed. Until then, I should be available, I should be online, so…
Ashiana.Griffith: Right. I think… I don't think he's gonna, like… I'm not trying to say, like, annoying, sorry, but, like, I don't think he's gonna…
Julia Matveyev: Yeah, that's okay.
Ashiana.Griffith: Alright, then. Alright, yeah, so just let me know for next week when you would like to meet. I'm not sure if it was best to meet with Mohammed first, but I'll message her, you can, like, text me or something.
Julia Matveyev: Yeah, that sounds good, definitely.
Ashiana.Griffith: All right, then. All right, Julia.
Julia Matveyev: All right, well, good meeting.
Ashiana.Griffith: Have a great day, bye!
Julia Matveyev: Yeah, you too.